Liza Mokhan



⟨ (+1) 682-000-9183⚠ liza.mokhan@gmail.com

A QA Automation Engineer with 4+ years of experience with great attention to details, an excellent academic record, with good understanding of software development lifecycle, good knowledge of software testing concepts and methodologies.

Looking for a challenging role in a high-level professional environment to utilize

My technical, math and communication skills.

EXPERIENCE

Quality Assurance Automation Engineer

MarTech Stack LLC

Oct 2019 - Dec 2020

- Developed, modified, and executed software test plans, automated scripts, and programs for testing.
- Increased the productivity of forms by analyzing test results, providing feedback, and consulting with development engineers in the resolution of various problems.
- Tracked software problems and verified their correction. Coordinated necessary testing resources to meet deadlines.

QA Engineer IT Royalty Feb 2014 – Dec 2014

- Investigated and analyzed requirements, specifications and technical documents for creating and maintaining well designed test documentation (test plans and test cases).
- Designed and executed complex SQL scripts to maintain data. Performed black-box testing, integration, regression, smoke, positive/negative testing.

QA Automation Software Testing Engineer

SmartSoft

Jan 2013 - Jan 2014

GMSP Risk Feed Quality Monitor: tool for checking big amounts of financial data via different business rules. Start-up company specialized in development and support of custom web and back-end solutions.

- Participated in daily/weekly meetings in accordance with Agile principles.
- Performed functional manual testing of UI (Web application).
- Implemented and maintained QA Automation tests using Selenium Webdriver and C#

Junior Software Testing Engineer

HealthCorp

Jun 2011 - Jul 2012

- Analyzed specification, added details, wireframes and screenshots to it.
- Performed functional manual testing on different phases of testing cycle.
- Performed usability testing. Reported issues into an owned bug-tracking system.

SKILLS

- Experience in Selenium (Webdriver), C#.
- Experience in SQL (MS SQL).
- Experience in Waterfall and Agile (Scrum, Kanban) methodologies.
- Experience in preparing and maintaining testing/technical documentation.
- Strong communication and self-organizing skills, troubleshooting and problem-solving skills.
- Strong work ethics, passionate and detail oriented, focused on result and quality, creative thinking, initiative
 and committed to project goals. Team player.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's degree (diploma cum laude) in Mathematics and computer science